hooters.com 2017-06-06

# Hooters Privacy Policy

Hooters of America (“Hooters”) takes your privacy very seriously. We are committed to protecting and safeguarding the privacy of visitors to our website, www.hooters.com, including mobile versions of our website (“Sites”), and users of our mobile device application, the Hoot Club (“Mobile App”). We welcome your questions and feedback on this Policy, and invite you to contact us.

This Privacy Policy identifies and describes the way Hooters uses and protects the information that we may collect about individuals who utilize the Sites. You can navigate to various portions of the Privacy Policy by clicking on the links below.

## The Personal Information We Collect

We may collect different types of personal and other information based on your use of our products and services and our relationship with you (“Personal Information”). Some examples of Personal Information we may collect include:

Information you give us.

  * Contact Information (such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, and e-mail address);
  * Information you provide in the context of one of Hooters’ Club memberships (such as favorite Hooters location and your birthday);
  * Payment information (such as your payment card details, financial account information, security codes, and billing address);
  * Purchase history (i.e., for Hoot Club members signed up for rewards, who provide purchase information via scanning restaurant receipts);
  * Information provided in an online job application (such as information about your education and work history and past salaries), or in a franchisee application;
  * Information provided by you in conjunction with an online sweepstakes entry, a survey, or a promotion;
  * Other personal information you may provide to us (including photographs).
  * Automatically-collected information.

Also, when you visit our Sites or Mobile App, we may collect certain information via automated means. For example, our systems may collect information about your activity on the Sites and Mobile App (i.e., pages you visit, address of a referring website (if any), identifiers for your mobile device, and Internet Protocal (IP) address) for a number of purposes. Such information is collected using automated technologies such as cookies, web beacons, and server log files. A “cookie” is a text file that our website would send to your computer or mobile device to identify your browser or to store information or settings in your browser. A “web beacon” (also known as a pixel tag or Internet tag) links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information through cookies back to a server. A “server log” tracks which webpages you visit on our Sites and which portions of the Mobile App you visit.

We may use this automatically-collected information to help tailor the ads you may see on the Sites and the messaging on the Mobile App. Further, we use this information to operate, maintain, and manage our Sites and Mobile App.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive certain types of cookies, and you can also set your browser to restrict or disable certain types of cookies. Please note that if you do restrict or disable cookies, you may not be able to use all the features of our Sites and Mobile App.

## Mobile devices and location information.

If you do not turn off GPS features on your mobile device, our Mobile App may collect information about the location of your device using technologies such as GPS, Wi-Fi, or cell tower proximity. This information is used to help with any location-based requests you may make (i.e., to find the nearest Hooters). For most mobile devices, you can withdraw your permission for Hooters’ systems to gather this information through your mobile device setting.

## How We Use The Personal Information We Collect

We may use the Personal Information we collect in a variety of ways, including to:

  * Provide you with the best customer experience possible;
  * Provide the products and services you purchase, and to respond to your questions;
  * Communicate with you regarding service updates, offers, special events, promotions, and sweepstakes;
  * Deliver customized content and advertising that may be of interest to you;
  * Address network integrity and security issues;
  * Create and manage a Hooters club membership (i.e., Hoot Club, Hoot e-Club, Hoot m-Club).
  * Evaluate job applications and respond to your inquiries into potential employment;
  * Evaluate franchisee applications;
  * Respond to your requests, questions, and/or comments;
  * Perform data analyses (including market and consumer research, and trend analyses)

## Personal Information We Share With Others

Hooters does not sell your Personal Information to third parties.

Hooters may share your personal information with parent companies, subsidiaries and affiliates (Hooters of America Companies, or “HOA Companies”), as well as with Hooters franchisees. (Franchisees are discussed further below.) Hooters requires these entities to comply fully with this Privacy Policy. Subject to applicable legal restrictions, the HOA Companies may share your Personal Information with each other to make sure your experience is as seamless as possible, and you have the full benefit of what Hooters has to offer. For example, if you select a Hooters franchise as your favorite Hooters location, that franchisee may be provided with Personal Information such as your contact information and birthday, in order to make special offers to you.

Hooters may share your Personal Information with non-HOA companies that perform services on our behalf, as necessary for them to perform those services. HOA requires those non-HOA companies to have reasonable safeguards in place to protect any Personal Information they may receive in a manner consistent with applicable law. Further, Hooters may share information collected by cookies and other automated means with sites you link to from the Sites or Mobile App, or social media providers (such as Twitter, Facebook, and Google+) that you visit by clicking through from our Sites or Mobile App. Please note that while Hooters does not capture or store your login information or any other personally identifiable information for Twitter, Facebook, and other social networks, their websites may store session information or cookies on your computer or wireless phone.

In Other Circumstances: Other than as noted above, we may provide Personal Information to non-HOA companies or other third parties for purposes such as:

  * Complying with court orders and other legal process;
  * To assist with identity verification, and to prevent fraud and identity theft;
  * Selling HOA Companies’ assets, or in process of arranging for the dissolution of the HOA Companies through bankruptcy; or
  * Enforcing our agreements and property rights.

## Anonymous & Aggregate Information

Hooters also collects some Personal Information on an anonymous basis, and/or anonymizes the Personal Information we collect about you. We obtain aggregate data by combining anonymous data that meet certain criteria into groups. When we employ non-HOA companies to anonymize or aggregate data on our behalf, Hooters requires those non-HOA companies to protect any Personal Information they may receive in a manner consistent with this Policy. We may share aggregate or anonymous information in various formats with trusted non-HOA companies, and may work with those entities to do research and provide products and services.

## Our Online Privacy Policy for Children

The Sites are not designed to attract children under the age of 13, and the Mobile App is designed to be used only by persons above 18 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personally identifying information from anyone under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a visitor under the age of 13, we will delete the information from our records. A child’s parent or legal guardian can request that Personal Information of their child be deleted from our records, if it has not been already. To make such a request, please contact us at the contact points provided below.

## Safeguarding Your Personal Information

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take reasonable steps to help ensure the privacy and security of your Personal Information. We have implemented encryption or other appropriate security controls to protect Personal Information when stored or transmitted by Hooters. We require non-HOA companies acting on our behalf to have reasonable safeguards in place to protect any Personal Information they may receive in a manner consistent with applicable law.

However, you understand and agree that such steps do not guarantee that use of the Sites is invulnerable to all security breaches, and that Hooters makes no warranty, guarantee, or representation that use of any of our Sites is protected from viruses, security threats or other vulnerabilities.

There are several measures you can take to protect your Personal Information. One option is simply not to volunteer it to us. The Federal Trade Commission’s site, www.ftc.gov, also offers useful information about how to protect personally-identifiable information provided online or through mobile applications.

## Links to Other Sites

We may offer links to sites or to social media providers that are not operated by Hooters. If you visit one of these linked sites, or access social media from our Sites or Mobile App, you should review the privacy and other policies of those other sites.

Please note that several third-party sites have limited licenses to use Hooters’ trademarks, but that those sites are not operated by Hooters. For example, there are independent companies who sell Hooters-branded products, process Hooters job applications, take entries into Hooters sweepstakes, and/or sell Hooters gift cards. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies, and any personal information you submit to those companies online is subject to their websites’ privacy policies, which we encourage you to review.

## Hooters Franchisees

Many Hooters restaurants are owned and operated by franchisees, who are independent owners of their own businesses, operating under an agreement with Hooters to use our trademarks and to receive other support for their business operations. Some franchisees operate their own websites and/or provide their own mobile device applications. These web sites and apps are not operated by Hooters, are are not subject to this Privacy Policy, and instead would have their own privacy policies that you should review.

Please keep in mind that if you visit a franchisee’s website (which would not be a www.hooters.com site) or a franchisee’s app (which would not be Hoot Club), a different privacy policy would apply to information you provide.

## Social Media and Personal Information

Hooters uses a variety of new technologies and social media options to communicate and interact with consumers, and has links to certain social media provider available on its Sites and Mobile App. When interacting with the Hooters presence on those websites, you may reveal certain Personal Information to Hooters or to third parties. Except when used by a Hooters employee for the purpose of responding to a specific message or request, Hooters will not use, share, or retain your Personal Information.

At this time, Hooters has four (4) Social Media accounts: https://www.facebook.com/hooters, https://twitter.com/hooters, https://instagram.com/hooters/, http://www.youtube.com/hooters, as well as a Google+ profile, with clickable links on the Sites and Mobile App to take visitors to the Hooters account at each of these locations. Hooters staff does not collect, use or disclose any information about visitors who comment or 'like' the Hooters’ Facebook site, link tweets to Hooters’ Twitter account or follow Hooters on Twitter or Instagram, or watch Hooters’ YouTube videos.

As noted above in the Franchisees section, Hooters Franchisees may sponsor their own Facebook Pages, Twitter Accounts, Instagram, and YouTube Accounts. Those franchisees operate under their own privacy policies.

Facebook: If you visit https://www.facebook.com/hooters, you can post comments or click on the 'like' option for individual entries posted by Hooters. If you comment or click on the 'like' button, personally identifying information will be visible to other Facebook site visitors to Hooters’ page, depending on your own Facebook privacy settings. Facebook’s site is governed by its own Privacy Policy, available at: <http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>.

Twitter: Hooters uses Twitter to send short messages or 'Tweets' to share information about Hooters Restaurants, as well as to respond to comments and inquiries sent to our Twitter account: @HOOTERS. If you are link a tweet to the @HOOTERS account, personally identifying information will be visible to visitors to Hooters’ Twitter feed, but you can modify how much of your Personal Information provided to Twitter is visible by changing your privacy settings at the Twitter.com website. The Twitter Privacy Policy is available at: <http://twitter.com/privacy>.

YouTube: Hooters also posts videos on YouTube. If you log on to YouTube and comment on any Hooters videos, any Personal Information you included when registering for your account will be visible to visitors who click on the comment on Hooters’ YouTube site. The YouTube Privacy Policy is available at: <http://www.youtube.com/t/privacy>.

Instagram: Hooters also posts pictures on Instagram. If you log onto Instagram and link to or comment on any such photos, the information or content that you had voluntarily disclosed to Instagram as part of your Profile will then be visible to visitors to Hooters’ Instagram account. The Instagram Privacy Policy is available at: <https://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/#>

## Notice to California Residents

Subject to certain limits under California Civil Code § 1798.83, California residents may ask us to provide them with (i) a list of certain categories of personal information that we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, and (ii) the identity of those third parties. To make this request, California residents may contact us as specified in the "How to Contact Us" section below.

## Your Consent

This Privacy Policy applies to all information gathered for and on behalf of Hooters through its Sites including, but not limited to www.hooters.com, together with any and all future websites operated by or on behalf of Hooters (collectively, the “Websites”), and to its Mobile App, together with any and all future mobile applications operated by or on behalf of Hooters (collectively, the “Applications”). By using the Websites or Applications, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Statement.

**BY SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO HOOTERS, AND/OR BY ACCESSING AND USING THE WEBSITES AND APPLICATIONS, YOU AGREE TO HOOTERS’ COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE OF SUCH PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

This Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. By continuing to use the Sites, you consent to any changes in this Policy. This Policy was last modified on 02/20/2015.

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, you may contact us using the information below.

_Email:_

privacy@hooters.com

_Mail:_

Privacy at Hooters   
Attn: Legal Department   
1815 The Exchange   
Atlanta, GA 30339

When contacting us, so that we can respond, please include your full name and the contact information for your preferred mode of contact (mail, email, or phone), and please describe the specific nature of your request.

Thank you.
